reviewspress.com 2009-03-09

# Privacy Policy | nine Marketing

## Privacy Policy

Neil Harvey and Nine Marketing is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase products or services through any of our Web sites must provide their name, email address (mailing address and phone number for physical products only). All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection via Paypal or 2Checkout.

All online visitor data collected by Neil Harvey | Nine Marketing is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Neil Harvey | Nine Marketing encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.

Check out the [FTC’s site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html) for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:

Neil Harvey | Nine Marketing [here](http://www.faqhelpdesk.com/)

## New Product Notifications

Signup below to receive an email alert when new products are available. Plus receive a discount coupon to use on any products listed at Nine Marketing!
